

ABOUT

I have saturated half-year experience with programming web-applications. I want to become a strong developer in the shortest time. In this way, I'm spending a lot of time for self-education and trying to be always in progress. In addition, there are no problem from me to be a part of team.

LANGUAGES

English - Advanced (EF SET Certificate) http://efset.org/cert/8pvbVm

CONTACTS

TELEPHONE:

+38 (067) 249 77 12

SOCIAL LINKS:



https://www.linkedin.c om/in/mykhailoklypalskyi-3a21b017b/



https://www.facebook. com/micishaca



https://github.com/Kly palskyi



https://join.skype.com/i nvite/e5tMso1CGLPi

E-MAIL:

klypalskyi@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Programming Computers (inside) Sport Traveling Self-education

MYKHAILO KLYPALSKYI

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

MAIN SKILLS

- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- GIT
- ES 6

- React.js
- JQuery
- **REST API**
- AJAX

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- SQL
- Node.is
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator

EXPERIENCE

IDEA BANK, Developer

09.2018 - NOW

Optimizing e-commerce monitoring with using JS, PHP, SQL skills. Making more useable web-application for inside documentation and reports. There are also some commercial cases for analytics and e-commerce monitoring with using HTML, CSS, JS, SQL, PHP, Node.js (Confidential)

SK WEAR ONLINE - https://klypalskyi.github.io/skwearonline/build/index.html with using HTML, CSS/SCSS, VanillaJS, GULP, GIT

FindPic - https://klypalskyi.github.io/FindPic/build/index.html with using HTML, CSS/SCSS, VanillaJS, WebPack, GIT

LLC DUET POWER, CEO

2014 - 2018

Start a business of distributing electric devises for energy-saving technology. It's like generators, batteries, solar panels etc.

EDUCATION

KYIV NATIONAL ECONOMIC UNIVERSITY

2009 - 2015

Higher economic education

GO IT COURSES

2018 - 2019

Learning for Full-Stack developer skills.

ABBEY COLLEGE

2009

English skills

EDUCATION PROJECTS

GO IT landing page - https://klypalskyi.github.io/Hackaton/build/index.html with using HTML, CSS, GULP, GIT